Viewers all over the world,
Let your confession be:
"Lord Jesus come into my heart."
"Wash me with your precious blood."
Then you can proceed.
You need Jesus to come into your heart
before you can speak with all of your heart.
before you can confess what is in your heart.
Right now ask Jesus to come into your heart.
Viewers report this prayer: Lord Jesus come into my heart.
Wash me with your precious blood in Jesus Christ name.
Viewers right now begin to speak to every infirmity.
Every spirit of infirmity command them to leave you right now!
Command them to leave your business.
Command them to leave your career.
Viewers all over the world, speak right now.
Begin to speak to every spirit of infirmity-within ...out of your :business, finances, family.
Command them to leave!
They must obey!
Viewers all over the world, begin to open your lips and begin to speak to ever spirit of infirmity.
Speak to every spirit of destruction, every spirit that kills, steals, and destroys.
Command them to leave!
They must obey!
Every knee shall bow.
Every tongue shall confess.
Jesus is Lord!
Confess it, confess it right now! Open your lips, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua. Touch your screen by faith in Jesus name.
Viewers all over the world, every sickness, every hidden affliction
in your: bone, kidney, liver and blood.
Every hidden affliction, I command them to leave you in the name of Jesus!
I command them to leave you in the name of Jesus!
I speak to every sickness.
I speak to every affliction
in your body, to leave you in the name of Jesus!
in your blood, in your bone.
In your blood. In your kidney.
In your liver, in the name of Jesus!
I command them to leave you in the name of Jesus!
Rejoice! Rejoice!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua. Touch your screen by faith in Jesus name.
We believe that you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up to date with the latest: prophecies, deliverances,services, and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church Of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV. Changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world.